[right hand] grasp blue block from left tower | [left hand] stabilize left tower
[right hand] place blue block on right structure | [left hand] stabilize left tower
[right hand] grasp yellow block from left tower | [left hand] stabilize left tower
[right hand] place yellow block on right structure | [left hand] stabilize left tower
[right hand] remove light green block from left tower and place on table
[right hand] remove teal block from left tower and place on table
[right hand] remove grey block from left tower and place on table | [left hand] remove red block and place on table
[right hand] remove yellow block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] remove blue block from right structure and place on table
[left hand] remove white block from right structure and place on table | [right hand] hold the light green block
[right hand] remove light green block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] remove yellow block from right structure and place on table
[right hand] remove blue block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] hold the structure
[right hand] remove red block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] remove green from right structure and place on table
[right hand] remove purple block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] hold the structure
[right hand] remove yellow block from right structure and place on table | | [left hand] hold the structure
[right hand] remove light blue block from right structure and place on table | [left hand] remove white from right structure and place on table
[both hands] scatter remaining blocks on table